digiprint-supplies.com 2018-09-03

# DIGIPRINT SUPPLIES

**IMPORTANT LEGAL NOTICE**

DIGIPRINT SUPPLIES™ is committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to http://www.digiprint-supplies.com. Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us

  **By using, registering or placing an order on this site, you consent to the collection and the use of your information under the terms of this policy.**

  **1\. Introduction**

 **1.1** This Privacy Policy forms part of the website terms and conditions of use and is a statement as to how we shall process your personal data. We take the security and privacy of you and your personal data very seriously and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy on line. Please be aware that communications over the internet, such as emails, are not secure unless they are encrypted. We do not accept any responsibility for any unauthorised access or loss of personal data beyond our control. You may access most areas of this site without registering with us. Certain areas of the site are only open to you if you register.

 **1.2** Our primary reason for collecting your personal data is to process your orders for goods from our site and provide you with the most efficient service possible. We do not anticipate collecting or processing Sensitive personal data about you.

 **1.3** This Privacy Policy may change from time to time so please check it periodically

 **2\. Processing personal data**

 **2.1** When you contact us via the "contact us " form on the site or email us, or register on the site we will collect personal data from you.

 **2.2** Personal information may also be obtained automatically by your internet browser or by us over the telephone.

 **2.3** When a User places an order for goods and subsequently submits payment for that order we will collect personal data.

 **2.4** The types of personal data which we may collect from you could include, for example, your name, your contact details (such as your address, telephone number and email address), credit card information and other information collected on registration or through the "contact us" form.

 **2.5** We may also collect non-personal data about your visit to our website through the use of cookies. This information may include, for example, the pages which you browse. This information helps us to better manage and develop the site.

 **2.6** We will process your personal data so that:

 **2.6.1** we can process your orders for goods from the site subject to the terms and conditions of the site;

 **2.6.2** we can fulfill our obligations to you under any contract for the supply of goods subject to the terms and conditions of the site;

 **2.6.3** we can deal with the general queries you raise from time to time through the "contact us " form on the site, by post, by email or by telephone;

 **2.6.4** we can process payment made by Users; and

 **2.6.5** we can process your registration details.

 **2.7** Other purposes for which we will process your personal data are:

 **2.7.1** the general administration of your records by us;

 **2.7.2** the general maintenance of our database and records by us;

 **2.7.3** for security purposes to protect your personal data held and/or processed by us;

 **2.7.4** for training our employees in respect of providing our service to you;

 **2.7.5** to maintain records of payments made by Users;

 **2.7.6** for our general marketing purposes unless you have notified us to the contrary; and

 **2.7.7** to check your details and identity with fraud protection agencies to prevent fraud,  to trace debtors, recover debts and to manage your accounts.

 **2.8** When you enter the site, your computer will automatically be issued with a cookie. Cookies in themselves do not identify the individual user, just the computer used. Many sites do this whenever a user visits their site in order to track traffic flows. If you wish to reject our cookie, you can configure your browser to do so (see 10 below), alternatively you can ask your internet browser to alert you when a cookie is being set up.

 **2.9** You acknowledge that by providing personal data to us, you consent to the processing of your personal data in accordance with this policy.

 **3\. Transfer of personal data**

 **3.1** .We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personal data to third parties

 **4\. Rights to prevent usage of personal data**

 **4.1** You have the right to object to your personal data being used for 'direct marketing' and/or 'host mailing' purposes. You can change your options in relation to the information you wish to receive at any time by contacting us by email at info@digiprint-supplies.com.

 **4.2** As mentioned above you can set your internet browser to refuse cookies or you can ask your internet browser to alert you when a cookie is being set up.

  **5\. Maintenance of your personal data**

 **5.1** We are committed to the security of your personal data. All of our employees with access to your personal data and/or are associated with the processing of that data are contractually obliged to respect the confidentiality of your personal data.

 **5.2** We have implemented technology measures and security policies to protect the personal data that we have in our control from unauthorised access, improper use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction or accidental loss

  **6\. General application of our Privacy Policy**

 **6.1** This Privacy Policy only applies to the collection and use of your personal data provided to us and not to personal data you may provide directly to third parties (including but without limitation to our suppliers or any of the manufacturers of the goods advertised on the site). Any third parties will have their own policies in respect of processing personal data you provide to them and/or your personal data that we may disclose to them in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

  **7\. Information contained on the Site**

 **7.1** While the Company endeavours to ensure that the information on this Site is correct, the Company does not warrant the accuracy and completeness of the material on this Site. The Company may make changes to the material on this Site or described in it, at any time without notice. The material on this Site may be out of date, and the Company makes no commitment to update such material.

 **7.2** The material on this Site is provided "as is", without any conditions, warranties or other terms of any kind. Accordingly, to the maximum extended permitted by law, the Company provides you with this Site on the basis that the Company excludes all representations, warranties and conditions and other terms (including without limitation, the conditions implied by law of satisfactory quality, fitness for purpose and the use of reasonable care and skill) which but for this legal notice might have effect in relation to this Site.

 **8\. Liability**

 **8.1** The Company, any other party (whether or not involved in creating, producing, maintaining or delivering this Site), and any of the Company's group companies and the officers, directors, employees, shareholders or agents of any of them, exclude all liability and responsibility for any amount or kind of loss or damage that may result to you or a third party (including without limitation, any direct, indirect, punitive or consequential loss or damages, or any loss of income, profits, goodwill, data, contracts, use of money, or loss or damages arising from or connected in any way to business interruption, and whether in tort (including without limitation negligence), contract or otherwise) in connection with this Site in any way or in connection with the use, inability to use or the results of use of this Site, any websites linked to this Site or the material on such websites, including but not limited to loss or damage due to viruses that may infect your computer equipment, software, data or other property on account of your access to, use of, or browsing this Site or your downloading of any material from this Site or any websites linked to this Site.

 **8.2** Nothing in this legal notice shall exclude or limit the Company's liability for:

 **\- 8.2.1** death or personal injury caused by the Company's negligence; or

 **\- 8.2.2** fraudulent misrepresentation; or

 **\- 8.2.3** any liability which cannot be excluded or limited under applicable law, including without limitation all relevant consumer law.

 If your use of material on this Site results in the need for servicing, repair or correction of equipment, software or data, you assume all costs thereof.

  **9\. Contact information**

 **9.1** If you have any queries about our processing or use of your personal data you should write, in the first instance to info@digiprint-supplies.com.

  **10\. Cookies**

Information on how to block cookies can normally be found within the help features of your browser. Information can also be found on the main browser websites;

[http://www.microsoft.com](http://www.microsoft.com/) (Internet Explorer)

<https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/microsoft-edge> (Microsoft Edge)

<https://www.google.com/intl/en/chrome/browser/>[ ](https://www.google.com/intl/en/chrome/browser/)(Google Chrome)

<https://www.mozilla.org/en-GB/firefox> (Mozilla Firefox)

<https://www.apple.com/safari/> (Apple Safari)
